Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Students Records, 1907-2015: Finding Aid AC136
University Archives
- Series 6: Student Discipline, 1905-2015; 62 boxes
  - Student Discipline Files, 1905-2015; 62 boxes (Box 1D-62D)
- Series 7: 2009 July Accession, 1993-2000, 1993-2009 April; 1 box; 2 items
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  AR.2009.079
  The July 2009 Accession series consists of files on alcohol policy and related topics, registrar scheduling proposals, Student Life, Health and Athletics Committee materials, Board of Trustees meeting materials, and other miscellaneous topics.
  The arrangement of the records at the time of transfer has been maintained.
  - Alcohol Policy Considerations, 1993-1999; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Press Coverage, 1993-1999; 1 box
    - University Alcohol Use and Policies, 1997-1999; 1 box (Box 73)
    - Princeton and Alcohol Issues, 1993-1997; 1 box (Box 73)
    - Eating Clubs and Alcohol, 1994-1997; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Registrar's Class Scheduling Proposals, 1996-1997; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Residential Colleges, 1994; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Student Initiatives, Harmony Club, circa 1995; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Trustee Initiative on Alcohol Abuse, 1998-1999; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Student Life, Health and Athletics Committee Materials, 1999; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Trustees Meeting Books, January, 2009 April; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Trustee Initiative, Updates from Constituencies, 1999; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Background Materials for Report to Trustees, 2000; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Committee on Nude Olympics, 1999; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Greek Organizations, 1999; 1 box (Box 73)
  - Series 7: 2009 July Accession, 1993-2000, undated; 1 item
- Series 8: Residential College Public Websites, 2015; 1 websites
  This series contains the public websites of Princeton's six residential colleges. The sites primarily consist of events, announcements, staff listings, and descriptions of student life opportunities sponsored by the College.
  Full text searching of these archived websites are available through the ArchiveIt interface.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by name of the college. Within each file, the websites retain their original order as when published by the respective College.
  - Butler College Public Website, 2015; 1 website
    The Butler College website provides information for undergraduate students living and studying at Butler. The website contains information on academic advising, dining, student groups, staff, and facilities. It also includes announcements and an event calendar.
    Full text searching of these archived websites are available through the Archive-It interface.
  - Forbes College Public Website, 2015; 1 website
    The Forbes College website publishes information for students in the college about the Forbes' people, events, and student life. The student life section of the website provides a short history of the college and describes a few of its sponsored activities, such as Conversation Tables and College Trips.
  - Mathey College Public Website, 2015; 1 website
    The Mathey College website provides information for students living and studying at Mathey College. The website includes information on academics and advising, college history, college spaces, and staff. There are also videos and photos of life at the college as well as a news feed and events calendar.
  - Rockefeller College Public Website, 2015; 1 website
    The Rockefeller College website provides information about the college for current students and their families. The website contains information on staff, places, academics, social life, and the history of the college. The website also includes a blog, and an events calendar.
  - Whitman College Public Website, 2015; 1 website
    This website, which is intended for use by Whitman students and their families, describes life in the college as well as provides information about the college's student governance, staff members, and faculty advisers. The website also contains materials about advising and the broader social opportunities in the college, such as intramural sports and the college's newsletter, The Whitmaniac.
  - Wilson College Public Website, 2015; 1 website
    The Wilson College website provides information to current students of the college. The website includes information on academics, student life, spaces, clubs and initiatives, and college history. The website also includes a news feed and events calendar.